<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Murtaza Haque&#39;s Website</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/</link>
        <description>Recent content on Murtaza Haque&#39;s Website</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thedarklynx786.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Four Horsemen</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/fourhorsemen/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/fourhorsemen/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/fourhorsemen/FourHorsemen.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Four Horsemen" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Four Horsemen&amp;rdquo; is the album I created where I wanted to play around with creating metal tracks on JummBox. Due to its very MIDI nature, JummBox only has one guitar feature for a distinctly &amp;ldquo;metal&amp;rdquo; sound. I wanted to try and play around with the tools in JummBox and transform this guitar sound into something more than just its preset.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The idea for the Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse was kind of random, it just popped into my head. I did think it would make for a really sick theme for a series of metal tracks, and so I decided to center this album from the perspective of the four horsemen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once again, this uses the Cm/Gm phrygian notes, the ones that produce a really sick metal sound. I have also used certain riffs and musical themes from many different inspirations, ranging from Slipknot to MASTER BOOT RECORD, though they may not be apparently obvious. Check out each of the track descriptions for more details.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Elementals OST</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/elementalsost/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/elementalsost/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/elementalsost/Spark%20Ops.png" alt="Featured image of post Elementals OST" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;This soundtrack was one I created while working in HackClub&amp;rsquo;s Arcade Summer Hackathon. I collaborated with a bunch of people to create a Roblox game, where I was the sound designer and track composer. I had a lot of fun, and I ended up creating some of my favorite tracks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The game was previously called SparkOps with the idea in mind that we can shoot electricity out of our guns as a game mechanic, but then we settled on using all the elements through runes and renamed the game Elementals. The image was one we AI-generated for the cover page of our game. Makes a sick album cover!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once again, it really never gets old: I keep using notes that revolve around G and Cm. When they work together, they efficiently create a metal or rock atmosphere, hence why Cm is my favorite key signature and why the notes that it plays around with are often used in metal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arcade required you to have a Github commit for each project you upload, so here is the &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://github.com/TheDarkLynx786/Elementals-OST&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Github Repo&lt;/a&gt; for all the tracks and SFX I have designed for the project. You can also get access to the JSON files, so you can remix and play around with what I made (Note to self, make this a feature for all the tracks!).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Contact</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/contact/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/contact/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Corporate Crusade Suite</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/corporatecrusadesuite/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/corporatecrusadesuite/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/corporatecrusadesuite/CorporateCrusade.png" alt="Featured image of post Corporate Crusade Suite" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is kind of my first &amp;ldquo;set&amp;rdquo; of tracks; calling it an album seems kinda wrong, so I&amp;rsquo;m deciding it to call it a &amp;ldquo;suite.&amp;rdquo; It started with the first track, &amp;ldquo;Corporate Crusade,&amp;rdquo; which was originally made for a game jam with 2 other friends of mine. Eventually I started working on the other tracks, and I soon wish to turn this into an OST for the actual game, which I will be trying to revive, develop, and finish into a decent top-down shooter. I don&amp;rsquo;t have much art to show because art is the one thing I&amp;rsquo;m lacking in game design, so I&amp;rsquo;ll keep a pixel art of the player sprite as a placeholder image for now. As I think of more level ideas, I will compose more tracks and maybe update these old ones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of these tracks use the key of C minor, and are centered primarly around the notes G, Ab, and F. Different variations give each track its own identity. I would say this is kind of similar to the Prelude tracks in ULTRAKILL, so there&amp;rsquo;s my inspiration.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Website Music Section</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/website-music-section/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/website-music-section/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/website-music-section/Composition.png" alt="Featured image of post Website Music Section" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve added a new Music Section to my site! It features all of the tracks I have worked on. This post is about a month old from when I am actually writing this (August 2nd, 2024), and that&amp;rsquo;s because it took some time to develop the music section into something I actually found suited my site. And it&amp;rsquo;s live! Go check it out &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://thedarklynx786.github.io/music/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Music Section!&lt;/a&gt; (Or you know, you can just click the tab in the sidebar).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It took quite some time to get lists working, so I eventually just defauted to using tile lists and making my own custom ones from the site&amp;rsquo;s theme. It worked really well! Gave me lot&amp;rsquo;s of CSS experience while I was at it. Future plans for the site do include using JavaScript to make more interactive elements. Let&amp;rsquo;s make this site more interesting, eh?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archives</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/archives/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/archives/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Music</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/music/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/music/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://thedarklynx786.github.io/music/Music%20Page%20Banner.png" alt="Featured image of post Music" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the music section of my website! I have been involved with music since the start of 2018 and I&amp;rsquo;m still running strong! I primarily play percussive instruments, though I have some knowledge of guitar and a little in piano. Here you can find covers that I&amp;rsquo;ve made or pieces that I have performed (Yet to be added).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also compose electronic music using an online DAW I found called &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.beepbox.co/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;&lt;strong&gt;BeepBox&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (developed by John Nesky) and a mod for BeepBox called &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://jummb.us/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;&lt;strong&gt;JummBox&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. I don&amp;rsquo;t really have FLStudio or any other professional DAWs, so this will have to work for now. It is really simple to learn and you can make some awesome tracks with it! Below showcase some of the tracks I have made.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you would like to remix some of my tracks, you are welcome to use the download buttons to import the JSONs into BeepBox/JummBox! Feel free to play around and make your own versions, edits, or fixes to the track, but please give credit if you are willing to share!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>6-26-2024 Bike Logs</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;evening-lakeside-ride---6262024&#34;&gt;Evening Lakeside Ride - 6/26/2024
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h1 id=&#34;distance-13-miles&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Distance: ~13 miles&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-logs&#34;&gt;The Logs
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;start&#34;&gt;Start
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had gotten done with some of my work at around 6:30 PM, and I thought there would be no better time for me to go for another bike ride, as I already went swimming just yesterday. After packing some water in a drawstring bag, I refilled some air in my tires and headed out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;gear-shift-issues&#34;&gt;Gear Shift Issues
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had to stop nearby at an elementary school because my gear shifter was malfunctioning. It seemed like a project for a later time, and since it didn&amp;rsquo;t alter the ride too much I let it go for now. I stopped again at the high school nearby to drink up some water. I ended up downing 70% of the bottle in one go. Should&amp;rsquo;ve drank water &lt;em&gt;before&lt;/em&gt; starting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;lakeside-neighborhood&#34;&gt;Lakeside Neighborhood
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I made my way through the labyrinthine neighbordhood that bordered the lakeside. I had to check maps several times to see if I was not lost, but a single long road had led me out. My legs were quite tired from swimming yesterday, and it just happened so that my gear shift was locked onto the highest setting (requiring the most strength out of my legs). Had to walk to bike some time as well as my quads began to feel a bit hot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;nature-trail&#34;&gt;Nature Trail
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I saw an elderly couple exit a nearby nature trail. Having seen this on the map before my trip, I decided to see what it was about. It was blanketed with trees, providing a nice shady area from the sun. Conveniently, it led me right to the city park, which just bordered the lake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;flooded-lake&#34;&gt;Flooded Lake
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lake had been flooding as of recent. On a slightly botched fishing trip the previous Saturday involving my cousins, we managed to find a fishing spot in what was originally a parking lot. The flooding was pretty bad, but it seemed to have abated ever so slightly today, as an area we visited near the lake before was not that flooded today. Still the beachside and the volleyball courts were all submerged, as well as many trees and picnic spots. Nevertheless, the lake never fails to provide a beautiful view, and I got some pretty cool pictures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-search-for-water&#34;&gt;The Search for Water
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;After realizing I had to get home in an hour, I had to rush home quite fast. I was quite thirsty however, and since I previously downed my entire stock of cold water, I looked nearby for a place to refill. I came across the local Mexican grocery market, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t happen to see any water fountains there. Upon asking the butcher there, it didn&amp;rsquo;t like that would have helped either as they were only able to understand Spanish. So I left and decided I would just drink at home. I could&amp;rsquo;ve grabbed some water at the local Fuzzy&amp;rsquo;s, but I thought it wasn&amp;rsquo;t worth the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What I did find of worth however was a water fountain station I managed to spot at a nearby park. This was a mediocre decision, as the water was warm and made me thirstier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;home-stretch-and-more-gear-shift-trouble&#34;&gt;Home Stretch (and More Gear Shift Trouble)
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The way back was also pretty straightfoward. I did have some problems with the gear shifting, now interfering with my pedalling. It seems like a project is due to get these back to workable condition. Nevertheless I did make it home and managed to get there just before my dad pulled into the driveway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;gallery&#34;&gt;Gallery
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/NeighborhoodLakeview.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;4032&#34;
	height=&#34;3024&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/NeighborhoodLakeview_hu80b3ba703ddd64d71145b579fd5142d6_3794108_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/NeighborhoodLakeview_hu80b3ba703ddd64d71145b579fd5142d6_3794108_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;A picture I took from inside the neighborhood.&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;133&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;320px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/OverflowingLake.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;4032&#34;
	height=&#34;3024&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/OverflowingLake_hu2e52a8502ab570a6a33de72b57233eb9_3674411_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/OverflowingLake_hu2e52a8502ab570a6a33de72b57233eb9_3674411_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;A view of the overflowing lake. That tree is knee-deep. Could trees have knees?&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;133&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;320px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/SubmergedBeach.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;4032&#34;
	height=&#34;3024&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/SubmergedBeach_hua5ec7f4c0d3bf6215ede61379378d40e_2977820_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/SubmergedBeach_hua5ec7f4c0d3bf6215ede61379378d40e_2977820_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;Photo of the beach without the beach, and the volleyball courts. Volleyball in the water does sound fun!&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;133&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;320px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/SubmergedTrees.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;4032&#34;
	height=&#34;3024&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/SubmergedTrees_hud2bd450a4bbefdf0a0b6817ae2e47e29_5551845_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/SubmergedTrees_hud2bd450a4bbefdf0a0b6817ae2e47e29_5551845_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;A photo of some submerged trees. Normally these would have made for some great shade.&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;133&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;320px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/CloseWaters.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;4032&#34;
	height=&#34;3024&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/CloseWaters_hu0f9f26ac398a6c42df617b54ee44601b_4902168_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/CloseWaters_hu0f9f26ac398a6c42df617b54ee44601b_4902168_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The water catches up to a nearby building. Lucky that place won&amp;rsquo;t be getting wet.&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;133&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;320px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/BanksideView.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;4032&#34;
	height=&#34;3024&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/BanksideView_hu5460d1ea435b5df994a00879658db80f_3360286_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/BanksideView_hu5460d1ea435b5df994a00879658db80f_3360286_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;A nice, bankside view of the flooded lake. The sun is soon to set.&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;133&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;320px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/SidewalkLakeview.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;4608&#34;
	height=&#34;3456&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/SidewalkLakeview_hu62319ba0dde072ab4753c7727fa9d51d_4067135_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/6-26-2024-bike-logs/SidewalkLakeview_hu62319ba0dde072ab4753c7727fa9d51d_4067135_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;A final view of the lake from the sidewalk, as well as some more submerged trees. The water touches the sidewalk!&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;133&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;320px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>About</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/about/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/about/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About Me
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m Murtaza Haque, and I&amp;rsquo;m a fervid programmer who loves to code stuff! I also do many other things that people refer to as &amp;lsquo;hobbies.&amp;rsquo; Combining these interests together, I made this website as an online warehouse or diary for all of the activities I undertake. You can expect to find many of my projects here as well as my personally curated blogs on some things that I like talking about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;so-what-can-you-expect-to-find-on-this-website&#34;&gt;So what can you expect to find on this website?
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Biking Tales&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MATH, OHH LOTS OF MATH&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Me performing music&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some of my own music&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other programming projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Occassional meme or two?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Website updates (no brainer)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep philosophical questions nobody asked for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;And more! I&amp;rsquo;ll see what I can add to this website now and then. I might even embed some games on this site.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>First post</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/first-post/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/first-post/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Funny, I actually never put any content on this post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First post of many! Stay tuned for more!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Ozymandias</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/ozymandias/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/ozymandias/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/ozymandias/OzymandiasMitryAnderson.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Ozymandias" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;I made this piece after playing around with some chords on a piano site (link on the main page). The progression was assisted by a really cool melody with a really cool preset, and soon it evolved into this track. I think the naming of this track was probably the best thing I&amp;rsquo;ve named, as the title seems to fit very well with how the track sounds. There is a cool music-box section and also a violin solo at the end, so check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is also the first track I made that was non-loopable and a full production.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Chill Jam</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/chill-jam/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/chill-jam/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/chill-jam/Chill.jpeg" alt="Featured image of post Chill Jam" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;This track was inspired by those weird but good sounding ethereal-aesthetic drones that you sometimes find on YouTube, and also a little bit by the OneShot OST. I also kind of wanted to encapsulate the feeling of stying nice and warm inside while it snows outside, which is certainly wishful thinking because there was no snow when I was creating this piece.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Experiments</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/experiments/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/experiments/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/experiments/Experiments.jpeg" alt="Featured image of post Experiments" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tracks showcased here are a bunch of play-around tracks I made before I got a little serious with making music on BeepBox/JummBox. They are pretty basic and a good place to look back to see how far I&amp;rsquo;ve come.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Links</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/links/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/links/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Here are some of my links to profiles I&amp;rsquo;ve set up on different social platforms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t normally use that much social media so there aren&amp;rsquo;t that many. I&amp;rsquo;ll keep this updated when I join any new platforms.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Search</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/search/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/search/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
