<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>music on Murtaza Haque&#39;s Website</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/categories/music/</link>
        <description>Recent content in music on Murtaza Haque&#39;s Website</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thedarklynx786.github.io/categories/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Elementals OST</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/elementals-ost/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/elementals-ost/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/elementals-ost/Spark%20Ops.png" alt="Featured image of post Elementals OST" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call me the Iron Chef of BeepBox, cus I&amp;rsquo;m COOKING!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I got involved in the creation of my first game soundtrack for a group of people. They seemed to like it quite a lot, and I certainly hope you all do to! You can listen to it here by clicking on the link &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/elementalsost/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;You should really just use the sidebar and find your way through&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once again, this soundtrack utilizes my signature scale, the Cm phyrgian scale. This time around however, I played around with volume control and and a bunch of other tools that I was somewhat unfamiliar with before, and I happened to get significantly richer sounds. A friend even wanted to sample &amp;ldquo;Bloodlust,&amp;rdquo; one of the tracks I made for this soundtrack. This composition was a big success, and I learned a whole lot about EQ filters and many different tools!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Four Horsemen</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/four-horsemen/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/four-horsemen/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/four-horsemen/FourHorsemen.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Four Horsemen" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following the game soundtrack I made and the volume control experiments I was undertaking, I decided to undertake a composition series that depicted the Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, and did I mention it was metal?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can go check it out here &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/fourhorsemen/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Use the sidebar :( Not that hard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once again I was playing around with the same musical scale, nothing new there, but my experience from the previous music tracks that I made had taught me a lot about volume control, and I ended up making some great metal-sounding tracks that didn&amp;rsquo;t sacrifice sound quality to maintain the distorted metal guitar sound.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am still releasing a few tracks, so keep a lookout for them! I&amp;rsquo;ll make an update post for when the whole project is finished.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Website Music Section</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/website-music-section/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/website-music-section/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://thedarklynx786.github.io/p/website-music-section/Composition.png" alt="Featured image of post Website Music Section" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve added a new Music Section to my site! It features all of the tracks I have worked on. This post is about a month old from when I am actually writing this (August 2nd, 2024), and that&amp;rsquo;s because it took some time to develop the music section into something I actually found suited my site. And it&amp;rsquo;s live! Go check it out &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://thedarklynx786.github.io/music/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Music Section!&lt;/a&gt; (Or you know, you can just click the tab in the sidebar).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It took quite some time to get lists working, so I eventually just defauted to using tile lists and making my own custom ones from the site&amp;rsquo;s theme. It worked really well! Gave me lot&amp;rsquo;s of CSS experience while I was at it. Future plans for the site do include using JavaScript to make more interactive elements. Let&amp;rsquo;s make this site more interesting, eh?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
