<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Bpbx-jmbx-tracks on Murtaza Haque&#39;s Website</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Bpbx-jmbx-tracks on Murtaza Haque&#39;s Website</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Elementals OST</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/elementalsost/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/elementalsost/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/elementalsost/Spark%20Ops.png" alt="Featured image of post Elementals OST" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;This soundtrack was one I created while working in HackClub&amp;rsquo;s Arcade Summer Hackathon. I collaborated with a bunch of people to create a Roblox game, where I was the sound designer and track composer. I had a lot of fun, and I ended up creating some of my favorite tracks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The game was previously called SparkOps with the idea in mind that we can shoot electricity out of our guns as a game mechanic, but then we settled on using all the elements through runes and renamed the game Elementals. The image was one we AI-generated for the cover page of our game. Makes a sick album cover!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once again, it really never gets old: I keep using notes that revolve around G and Cm. When they work together, they efficiently create a metal or rock atmosphere, hence why Cm is my favorite key signature and why the notes that it plays around with are often used in metal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arcade required you to have a Github commit for each project you upload, so (the only time I&amp;rsquo;m ever going to do this), here is the &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://github.com/TheDarkLynx786/Elementals-OST&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Github Repo&lt;/a&gt; for all the tracks and SFX I have designed for the project. You can also get access to the JSON files, so you can remix and play around with what I made (Note to self, make this a feature for all the tracks!).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Corporate Crusade Suite</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/corporatecrusadesuite/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/corporatecrusadesuite/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/corporatecrusadesuite/CorporateCrusade.png" alt="Featured image of post Corporate Crusade Suite" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is kind of my first &amp;ldquo;set&amp;rdquo; of tracks; calling it an album seems kinda wrong, so I&amp;rsquo;m deciding it to call it a &amp;ldquo;suite.&amp;rdquo; It started with the first track, &amp;ldquo;Corporate Crusade,&amp;rdquo; which was originally made for a game jam with 2 other friends of mine. Eventually I started working on the other tracks, and I soon wish to turn this into an OST for the actual game, which I will be trying to revive, develop, and finish into a decent top-down shooter. I don&amp;rsquo;t have much art to show because art is the one thing I&amp;rsquo;m lacking in game design, so I&amp;rsquo;ll keep a pixel art of the player sprite as a placeholder image for now. As I think of more level ideas, I will compose more tracks and maybe update these old ones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of these tracks use the key of C minor, and are centered primarly around the notes G, Ab, and F. Different variations give each track its own identity. I would say this is kind of similar to the Prelude tracks in ULTRAKILL, so there&amp;rsquo;s my inspiration.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Ozymandias</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/ozymandias/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/ozymandias/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/ozymandias/OzymandiasMitryAnderson.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Ozymandias" /&gt;</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Chill Jam</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/chill-jam/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/chill-jam/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/chill-jam/Chill.jpeg" alt="Featured image of post Chill Jam" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;This track was inspired by those weird but good sounding ethereal-aesthetic drones that you sometimes find on YouTube, and also a little bit by the OneShot OST. I also kind of wanted to encapsulate the feeling of stying nice and warm inside while it snows outside, which is certainly wishful thinking because there was no snow when I was creating this piece.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Experiments</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/experiments/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/experiments/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://thedarklynx786.github.io/bpbx-jmbx-tracks/experiments/Experiments.jpeg" alt="Featured image of post Experiments" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tracks showcased here are a bunch of play-around tracks I made before I got a little serious with making music on BeepBox/JummBox. They are pretty basic and a good place to look back to see how far I&amp;rsquo;ve come.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
