<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>cooking on Murtaza Haque&#39;s Website</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx.com/categories/cooking/</link>
        <description>Recent content in cooking on Murtaza Haque&#39;s Website</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thedarklynx.com/categories/cooking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>My Special Omelette Recipe</title>
        <link>https://thedarklynx.com/p/my-special-omelette-recipe/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://thedarklynx.com/p/my-special-omelette-recipe/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://thedarklynx.com/p/my-special-omelette-recipe/Finished.jpg" alt="Featured image of post My Special Omelette Recipe" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;*Images Coming Soon*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;do-you-want-to-spice-your-breakfast-up-a-little-bit&#34;&gt;Do you want to spice your breakfast up a little bit?
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well I&amp;rsquo;ve got the perfect recipe! This innovative and transformative omelette recipe is sure to leave the consumers of your food mildy amused!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just check out these reviews!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Looks like&amp;hellip;green eggs&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;-One of my chemistry classmates in 10th grade&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s great!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;-My 10th grade chemistry teacher&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;OMG I LOVE IT BEST THING EVER!!!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;-My brother&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hey it&amp;rsquo;s actually not bad&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;-My cousin&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;At this point you are using half my spice cabinet, move out already you liability&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;-(Not) My Mom&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not convinced? Well then just check out the recipe yourself!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;heres-the-recipe&#34;&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s the Recipe
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-1---egg&#34;&gt;Step 1 - Egg
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;First find eggs. I think you may need eggs for this one (I recommend 2).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get a bowl and something to beat your eggs with (like a fork) and beat up your eggs, with the yolk of course. Get it into a nice, even, yellow goop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-2---spices-phase-1&#34;&gt;Step 2 - Spices Phase 1
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Get out some red chili powder and a good amount of salt. What, you expected quantities? Well, uhh, I&amp;rsquo;ll add them later I guess&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mix it up!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-3---spices-phase-2&#34;&gt;Step 3 - Spices Phase 2
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now listen carefully, you are gong to need:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Italian Seasoning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Garlic Powder (Too much works somehow)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paprika (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Garam Masala Powder (HIGHLY RECOMMENDED)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shawarma Powder (substitute for GMP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lemon-Pepper Seasoning (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meat Tenderizer (optional; I actually never put this one in, and I likely don&amp;rsquo;t recommend it. Try it if you want)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cumin Powder&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;del&gt;Illicit substances, because at this point we&amp;rsquo;ve reached this far&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Okay for legal purposes, please ignore that last item.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still think I don&amp;rsquo;t belong in an asylum yet? Good! Now let&amp;rsquo;s continue making our omelette. Just to remind you, we are making an omelette.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And once again, mix it all up! Ignore the possibly weird color, we are making the mother of all omelettes here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-4---oil-and-pan&#34;&gt;Step 4 - Oil and Pan
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Get a (hopefully non-stick) pan and some olive oil. Let it heat up until the oil flows fast on the pan (or you see olive oil vapor).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While this sits, move on to the next steps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-5---solid-ingredients&#34;&gt;Step 5 - Solid Ingredients
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that we&amp;rsquo;ve cleared the spices, let&amp;rsquo;s add some solid ingredients:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cheese (preferrably provalone or sharp cheddar)
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;(Hold off putting this in the bowl for now, unless it&amp;rsquo;s shredded cheese)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Onions (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chopped garlic (optional, recommended)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Milk (this is a legitimate ingredient, helps fluffen up the egg)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prepare to add them to the pan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-6---bread&#34;&gt;Step 6 - Bread
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is to transform your omelette into a sandwich, and is what I normally do. Ignore if you just want to omelette.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Toast some bread while you&amp;rsquo;re waiting for your pan to heat up. I currently have sourdough, but any bread of your taste will suffice. Toasting the bread adds a crunch, though you may not need to toast it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-7---cook&#34;&gt;Step 7 - Cook
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once your pan is hot enough, pour the egg batter onto the pan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While waiting for one side to cook, start shredding your cheese up into bits and putting them on the top side of the cooking egg. If it&amp;rsquo;s shredded cheese, add a spoonfull more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once the egg is hot enough, flip it over and let it cook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To avoid burning the cheese, flip it over quite frequently and move the egg around to not let the cheese stick to the pan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And finally, once both sides look good, sprinkle some italian seasoning and maybe some more cheese on top, and turn the stove off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-8---serve&#34;&gt;Step 8 - Serve
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prepare your bread. Fold up the omelette and place on the bread.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to, add a condiment on the other slice of bread before making it into a sandwich.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you don&amp;rsquo;t have bread, simply roll up and serve like normal, and add some condiments to the side. Be artsy with the presentation!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;wow-you-did-it&#34;&gt;Wow you did it!!
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now you can serve half-michellen-star, half-mediocre eggs to any guest you have over in the morning. This actually tastes good, trust. Feel free to play around with different steps in the process and experiment with your own egg recipe.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I swear I&amp;rsquo;ll add images later I&amp;rsquo;m doing college apps please&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
